resortsandlodges.com 2012-11-11

# Privacy Policy - ResortsandLodges.com

**Effective:** September 14, 2007

Your privacy on the Internet is very important to us. We recognize that when you provide us with information about yourself that you trust us to use your information responsibly. We believe your information should only be used to help us provide you with better service. That's why we have a policy to protect your personal information. This statement sets forth our privacy policy for ResortsandLodges.com®, describing the practices we follow to respect the privacy of all visitors. 

#### Our Commitment To Your Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

#### The Information We Collect

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the ResortsandLodges.com® website. On some Pages, you can make requests, and register to receive special offers. The types of personal information collected at these Pages are: Name, Address, Email address, Phone number 

#### “Cookies”

ResortsandLodges.com® and any of its governed sections may use “cookies.” A “cookie” is technology that allows our site to store tokens of information (an “identifier”) in your browser used only by our site while you are on our site. Cookies are not used to determine the personal identity of anyone merely visiting our website. They help us track traffic patterns so that we know which Areas of our site Users like and don't like. 

Cookies have other uses as well. In the client log-in and traveler log-in sections, cookies are used to provide entry for subscribers who have chosen the “automatic log-on” feature during registration. Cookies allow our technology to provide current navigation stream in the “navigation crumb” atop every page of our website, so that you can easily follow your path and return to previous Pages with ease. Cookies are also used to prevent online poll participants from voting more than once on a particular issue. 

If you do not want to receive a cookie from ResortsandLodges.com®, you have the option of setting your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie so that you may determine whether to accept it or not (see your browser settings to do that). However, please be aware that if you do turn off ”cookies” in your browser, you will not be able to fully experience some features on our website such as automatic log-on and other personalization features. 

#### The Way We Use Information

We use the information you provide about yourself through our Members Area to better understand the needs of our visitors and to provide you with timely offers that we best fit your interests. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

#### Our Commitment To Data Security

ResortsandLodges.com® has technological and operational security functions in place to protect personally identifiable information from loss, misuse, alteration or destruction. The data you may provide is shared only with authorized employees of ResortsandLodges.com®. Access to your information is limited by need, and those who have access to the data have agreed to maintain the confidentiality of such information. In addition, ResortsandLodges.com® may disclose personally identifiable information as may be required by subpoena, search warrant, or other legal process. 

#### Our Commitment To Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

#### How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

You can access and maintain all your personally identifiable information by signing in to our Members Area. The MySpot tab is located in the upper right corner of every page on ResortsandLodges.com®. 

#### Changes to This Policy

ResortsandLodges.com® may change this policy statement as needed. If changes to the statement are made, please note that it may take up to 30 business days before new privacy practices are implemented. 

#### How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at +1 (866) 757-8229 or send us an email at [support@resortsandlodges.com](mailto:support@resortsandlodges.com).
